    export const chapter10StudyData = [
      // Key Terms
      {
        id: "KT1001",
        front: "anorexia nervosa",
        back: "eating disorder characterized by an individual maintaining body weight that is well below average through starvation and/or excessive exercise"
      },
      {
        id: "KT1002",
        front: "bariatric surgery",
        back: "type of surgery that modifies the gastrointestinal system to reduce the amount of food that can be eaten and/or limiting how much of the digested food can be absorbed"
      },
      {
        id: "KT1003",
        front: "basolateral complex",
        back: "part of the brain with dense connections with a variety of sensory areas of the brain; it is critical for classical conditioning and attaching emotional value to memory"
      },
      {
        id: "KT1004",
        front: "binge eating disorder",
        back: "type of eating disorder characterized by binge eating and associated distress"
      },
      {
        id: "KT1005",
        front: "bisexual",
        back: "emotional and erotic attractions to both same-sexed individuals and opposite-sexed individuals"
      },
      {
        id: "KT1006",
        front: "body language",
        back: "emotional expression through body position or movement"
      },
      {
        id: "KT1007",
        front: "bulimia nervosa",
        back: "type of eating disorder characterized by binge eating followed by purging"
      },
      {
        id: "KT1008",
        front: "Cannon-Bard theory of emotion",
        back: "physiological arousal and emotional experience occur at the same time"
      },
      {
        id: "KT1009",
        front: "central nucleus",
        back: "part of the brain involved in attention and has connections with the hypothalamus and various brainstem areas to regulate the autonomic nervous and endocrine systems' activity"
      },
      {
        id: "KT1010",
        front: "cognitive-mediational theory",
        back: "our emotions are determined by our appraisal of the stimulus"
      },
      {
        id: "KT1011",
        front: "components of emotion",
        back: "physiological arousal, psychological appraisal, and subjective experience"
      },
      {
        id: "KT1012",
        front: "cultural display rule",
        back: "one of the culturally specific standards that govern the types and frequencies of emotions that are acceptable"
      },
      {
        id: "KT1013",
        front: "distorted body image",
        back: "individuals view themselves as overweight even though they are not"
      },
      {
        id: "KT1014",
        front: "drive theory",
        back: "deviations from homeostasis create physiological needs that result in psychological drive states that direct behavior to meet the need and ultimately bring the system back to homeostasis"
      },
      {
        id: "KT1015",
        front: "emotion",
        back: "subjective state of being often described as feelings"
      },
      {
        id: "KT1016",
        front: "excitement",
        back: "phase of the sexual response cycle that involves sexual arousal"
      },
      {
        id: "KT1017",
        front: "extrinsic motivation",
        back: "motivation that arises from external factors or rewards"
      },
      {
        id: "KT1018",
        front: "facial feedback hypothesis",
        back: "facial expressions are capable of influencing our emotions"
      },
      {
        id: "KT1019",
        front: "gender dysphoria",
        back: "diagnostic category in DSM-5 for individuals who do not identify as the gender associated with their biological sex"
      },
      {
        id: "KT1020",
        front: "gender identity",
        back: "individual's sense of being male or female"
      },
      {
        id: "KT1021",
        front: "habit",
        back: "pattern of behavior in which we regularly engage"
      },
      {
        id: "KT1022",
        front: "heterosexual",
        back: "emotional and erotic attractions to opposite-sexed individuals"
      },
      {
        id: "KT1023",
        front: "hierarchy of needs",
        back: "spectrum of needs ranging from basic biological needs to social needs to self-actualization"
      },
      {
        id: "KT1024",
        front: "homosexual",
        back: "emotional and erotic attractions to same-sexed individuals"
      },
      {
        id: "KT1025",
        front: "instinct",
        back: "species-specific pattern of behavior that is unlearned"
      },
      {
        id: "KT1026",
        front: "intrinsic motivation",
        back: "motivation based on internal feelings rather than external rewards"
      },
      {
        id: "KT1027",
        front: "James-Lange theory of emotion",
        back: "emotions arise from physiological arousal"
      },
      {
        id: "KT1028",
        front: "leptin",
        back: "satiety hormone"
      },
      {
        id: "KT1029",
        front: "metabolic rate",
        back: "amount of energy that is expended in a given period of time"
      },
      {
        id: "KT1030",
        front: "morbid obesity",
        back: "adult with a BMI over 40"
      },
      {
        id: "KT1031",
        front: "motivation",
        back: "wants or needs that direct behavior toward some goal"
      },
      {
        id: "KT1032",
        front: "obese",
        back: "adult with a BMI of 30 or higher"
      },
      {
        id: "KT1033",
        front: "orgasm",
        back: "peak phase of the sexual response cycle associated with rhythmic muscle contractions (and ejaculation)"
      },
      {
        id: "KT1034",
        front: "overweight",
        back: "adult with a BMI between 25 and 29.9"
      },
      {
        id: "KT1035",
        front: "plateau",
        back: "phase of the sexual response cycle that falls between excitement and orgasm"
      },
      {
        id: "KT1036",
        front: "polygraph",
        back: "lie detector test that measures physiological arousal of individuals as they answer a series of questions"
      },
      {
        id: "KT1037",
        front: "refractory period",
        back: "time immediately following an orgasm during which an individual is incapable of experiencing another orgasm"
      },
      {
        id: "KT1038",
        front: "resolution",
        back: "phase of the sexual response cycle following orgasm during which the body returns to its unaroused state"
      },
      {
        id: "KT1039",
        front: "satiation",
        back: "fullness; satisfaction"
      },
      {
        id: "KT1040",
        front: "Schachter-Singer two-factor theory of emotion",
        back: "emotions consist of two factors: physiological and cognitive"
      },
      {
        id: "KT1041",
        front: "self-efficacy",
        back: "individual's belief in his own capabilities or capacities to complete a task"
      },
      {
        id: "KT1042",
        front: "set point theory",
        back: "assertion that each individual has an ideal body weight, or set point, that is resistant to change"
      },
      {
        id: "KT1043",
        front: "sexual orientation",
        back: "emotional and erotic attraction to same-sexed individuals, opposite-sexed individuals, or both"
      },
      {
        id: "KT1044",
        front: "sexual response cycle",
        back: "divided into 4 phases including excitement, plateau, orgasm, and resolution"
      },
      {
        id: "KT1045",
        front: "transgender hormone therapy",
        back: "use of hormones to make one's body look more like the opposite-sex"
      },
      {
        id: "KT1046",
        front: "Yerkes-Dodson law",
        back: "simple tasks are performed best when arousal levels are relatively high, while complex tasks are best performed when arousal is lower"
      },
      // Review Questions
      {
        id: "R1001",
        front: "Need for ________ refers to maintaining positive relationships with others.",
        back: "affiliation"
      },
      {
        id: "R1002",
        front: "________ proposed the hierarchy of needs.",
        back: "Abraham Maslow"
      },
      {
        id: "R1003",
        front: "________ is an individual's belief in her capability to complete some task.",
        back: "self-efficacy"
      },
      {
        id: "R1004",
        front: "Carl mows the yard of his elderly neighbor each week for $20. What type of motivation is this?",
        back: "extrinsic"
      },
      {
        id: "R1005",
        front: "According to your reading, nearly ________ of the adult population in the United States can be classified as obese.",
        back: "one third"
      },
      {
        id: "R1006",
        front: "________ is a chemical messenger secreted by fat cells that acts as an appetite suppressant.",
        back: "leptin"
      },
      {
        id: "R1007",
        front: "________ is characterized by episodes of binge eating followed by attempts to compensate for the excessive amount of food that was consumed.",
        back: "bulimia nervosa"
      },
      {
        id: "R1008",
        front: "In order to be classified as morbidly obese, an adult must have a BMI of ________.",
        back: "40 or more"
      },
      {
        id: "R1009",
        front: "Animal research suggests that in male rats the ________ is critical for the ability to engage in sexual behavior, but not for the motivation to do so.",
        back: "medial preoptic area of the hypothalamus"
      },
      {
        id: "R1010",
        front: "During the ________ phase of the sexual response cycle, individuals experience rhythmic contractions of the pelvis that are accompanied by uterine contractions in women and ejaculation in men.",
        back: "orgasm"
      },
      {
        id: "R1011",
        front: "Which of the following findings was not a result of the Kinsey study?",
        back: "Sexual desire and sexual ability can be separate functions."
      },
      {
        id: "R1012",
        front: "If someone is uncomfortable identifying with the gender normally associated with their biological sex, then he could be classified as experiencing ________.",
        back: "gender dysphoria"
      },
      {
        id: "R1013",
        front: "Individuals suffering from posttraumatic stress disorder have been shown to have reduced volumes of the ________.",
        back: "hippocampus"
      },
      {
        id: "R1014",
        front: "According to the ________ theory of emotion, emotional experiences arise from physiological arousal.",
        back: "James-Lange"
      },
      {
        id: "R1015",
        front: "Which of the following is not one of the seven universal emotions described in this chapter?",
        back: "melancholy"
      },
      {
        id: "R1016",
        front: "Which of the following theories of emotion would suggest that polygraphs should be quite accurate at differentiating one emotion from another?",
        back: "James-Lange theory"
      }
    ];